Hello there!
Excuse us.
Well, old woman, what kind of mischief
do you want to get into today?
So many options.
We could stew up fresh
meat until it's nearly
falling apart and then stew it some more.
They're either stew stands or
there's not a lot to do around here.
I hate to interrupt, but isn't
this the Hunters Association?
Bye, Jiminy.
Looks like we have company.
You must be those hunters
the Clear Flow Lake
director said were coming
to challenge the stratum.
Yep, that's us.
I was hoping you could give us
a few pointers or something.
That's why I'm here.
We even have materials prepared for you.
I'll go get them.
This place used to be bustling with
hunter types just a handful of years ago.
But then that one fella
conquered the right-hand path.
Ever since he came back
carrying the belongings
of his friends who starved
to death along the way,
it's been pretty quiet around here.
That'll do it.
We've scored more tasty knowledge.
Somehow there's never been a
single monster attack here.
And while the middle and left-hand
paths have been attempted,
even after half a year of pushing
forward, there was still no end in sight.
It would seem the rumors are true.
It's a tradition for hunters to
bring along red metal stakes.
Before turning back, they put those suckers
in the ground to mark how far they got.
So yeah, basically when we stop seeing
these, we've gone deeper than anyone else.
We're going to make it all
the way to the very end,
so I doubt we'll get a chance
to leave one ourselves.
Whatever you say.
By the way,
you can take the cart the Clear Flow
Lake director gave us the other day.
We've got no use for that
darn thing around here.
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box,
but inside, I've still got a human soul!
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super-strong partner, Lamas!
The name's Boxxo. Hello there!
That means yes, by the way.
Its up to me.
I've got digital.
Hm I'm so sorry.
That's my head.
I've got nothing but.
No one can die.
I can just see you. You can see it.
I've got a flash drive.
I'm so sorry.
I can see it. Take it.
I gather the talent.
There's a ton of.
I'll see you
next time.
There aren't any Unasusu.
Hello there.
The time has finally come to
wow them with my new powers.
I'm rank three, baby!
Let's do this!
Form change!
What's that?
Um, Boxo, care to explain?
It's a vending machine with
a slick two-seater ride.
I've never seen anything like this!
It's too large to be a shoe, unless
it's for Dog Mountain. Pity likes.
Is it for Boxo and me?
I could get used to this.
I don't know what manner of magic
this is, but it's quite remarkable.
This car is technically a dispensed good,
which means there's no
time limit on this bad boy.
It has four wheels, so maybe
it's some kind of covered wagon?
Though I've never seen one quite like it.
Oh, maybe they'll get the hint
if I change into a gas pump.
Rank three way extended
my telekinesis range.
Now I'm a smooth operator.
I never thought I'd
realize my dream of burning
rubber as a vending
machine in another world.
That's amazing, Boxxo.
You're full of surprises.
I see. Pretty clever.
Leave it to me, Voxo.
Beast that she is, Hulemy is remodeling
the wagon so we can hitch it to the car.
Kind of dark.
Can you make it a little brighter?
Hello there.
Great.
Now it's perfect.
Making stuff's easier when you can see.
That thing.
Director Bear wants us to open whatever
this is when we make it
to the deepest point.
Well, I'll try my best to
keep it safe until then.
When Hulimi's knee-deep in a new
project, she'll sometimes forget to eat.
I'd better tempt her tongue
with some packaged goodies.
What the heck?
I'm trying to work, you know
Right, water.
I guess I'll take a short break.
I couldn't believe my eyes when you suddenly
popped out that weird-looking wagon.
What do you call that thing?
A car!
It's an A car?
That's pretty cool.
Oof, I'll just have to let that one slide.
Once the wagon work is done, I'll take
Hulemy here for a pleasure cruise.
Bet it wouldn't take her
long to learn how to drive.
I have no idea how fast
our new A-car can travel,
but I'm certain it will
save us a lot of time.
So thank you.
Though honestly, I wouldn't mind it,
traveling with you for years to come.
Agreed.
Now, better keep at it.
Hulemy stayed up all night working.
And like always, she pulled it off.
Let's head out.
Whoa, it's so fast!
I don't exactly get what's powering it?
My butt isn't even getting sore from
the vibration, which is pretty wild.
This is way faster than an Unasusu.
There's a breeze.
It feels nice on my skin.
I find it quite invigorating.
Master Boxo, our hero.
Look who's Mr.
Popular now.
It's going to be a long trip, but
hopefully this makes things more enjoyable.
We quickly got to the fork in the road.
With our new wheels, the trip
was off to a great start.
Weapon maintenance,
chatting, smelling shoes.
Everyone spent their time
however they saw fit.
Today's the day I'm gonna beat you!
In time,
they started taking two-hour breaks
every day, which included sparring,
and whatever that is, to
help them stay in shape.
They stayed active, ate and slept
well, And were mindful of their health.
The team was in tip-top shape.
For entertainment, I've been playing
cinematic masterpieces on my nav system.
For those on the wagon, I provided card
games and toys to battle the boredom blues.
You made a fatal mistake, Shui.
Say hello to my little
friend, the trap card. Boom!
I lost again!
I demand a rematch!
One hundred four.
One hundred five?
Anyone else notice we haven't
seen those red steaks in a while?
Good point, I don't think I've
spotted a single one since yesterday.
Maybe we've already set a
new record down this path!
I don't know.
We've only been at it a week.
That's true, but perhaps our
speed has made it possible.
Does that make any kind of sense, Master?
Yes.
Whenever my pals are in
dreamland, I start hauling it.
Go in a fast yet sensible
80 kilometers per hour.
If I keep this up, which I shall,
we'll be partying in the
inner depths in no time flat.
Over there, something is approaching us.
they appear to be monsters
though i thought there were
none to be found in here so
much for that theory what do we
do now i shall lead the attack
and safeguard our journey
please just sit back and relax
master boxo let me at him
coach seems we've got ourselves
a bushel of eager beavers
makes sense they've been
training non-stop so they're
probably dying to let off
a little steam not so fast
something's off they might be the
hunters that went in before us
Holy moly, it's Aka and Shiro!
Help us.
Before it's too late, we're done if
we don't get some food and fizzy.
I beg if I weren't busy dying.
Boxo, volume number six.
What happened to Captain
Kerioyl and the Vice-Captain?
It's bad!
They're both further up from here.
Maybe we've told a fib here and there,
but I swear we're not working
for the Netherlord anymore.
We know it's kind of an awkward
time to hit you up for more favors,
but please help them.
Boxxo, have mercy on us.
Hello there.
Given their pathetic display, how
could we refuse their request?
After what happened on the roof,
he was suspicious that we had
somehow helped Boxo escape.
He accused Sulream of the same thing.
We realized he was
planning to get rid of us.
Sulream transferred the whole family
here, including our big brother.
But breaking free of the Netherlord's
restraint spell and then having
no choice but to perform a transfer
left her too drained to move.
Interesting,
so in the end she chose to betray the
Netherlord We walked for a week straight
with barely any food Because we knew our
only hope was crossing paths with you guys
We left the others with even less food
They insisted this was the only option
That's why we've got to hurry I don't
think they'll be able to last much longer
Don't you worry,
we're in Bokso's super-fast
day car That's right,
we'll be there in a
flash Then I'm gonna nap
I know we'll make it in
time, so you can nap away
Time to show off the
driving skills I honed
during my nationwide
vending machine pilgrimage
We're creeping up on suppertime,
I've covered a lot of ground
the first road trip in another
world almost ended in the first
car crash wait is this a wagon
or something hello there is that
you hello old friend you've
become another weird shape i see
wait if you're here where are
the boys with us that's a relief
They're breathing, it's
not too late I breach
We used a temporary sleep spell To
conserve what little strength they had left
Is that Eulamy?
And everyone else?
As they say, all's well that vends well.
I'll hook them up with the same meal
deal I gave the red and white twins.
I won't accept a handout from a human.
You have to drink it, Big Sis.
If you don't, you're gonna die.
Didn't love the sentiment,
but at least she spoke.
It's almost impressive that she's sticking
to her bigoted little
guns on hating humans.
All clear.
I took a long sip for you just to make
sure they didn't put any poison in it.
Please drink it.
Well, if it means that much
to you, I suppose I could try.
This alliance might be
inappropriately easy to pull off!
Is it safe to say you guys
are done being spineless
little cowards who do whatever
the Netherlord tells you to?
That about sums it up.
Forget obeying and we
can't even go near the guy!
He'd kill every last one of us.
That said, we still can't defy Solween
on account of our son's predicament?
There's nothing I can vend
to change the bitter truth.
She has Kai's life in her hands.
You're just like us because you
can't go back to the Netherlord.
So we should stick together.
No, I can't.
I despise humans.
But I'm human too.
Does that mean you hate me?
Pixis?
Don't be ridiculous.
Those are entirely different subjects.
No, they're not.
If you refuse to trust
humans, at least trust me.
I swear on my very soul
I would never betray you.
I love you with all my heart!
Fine, if you insist.
I suppose I'll cooperate
for the time being.
But don't expect me to get friendly.
Thanks a bunch!
You're the best!
Well, my skin is crawling.
But on the bright side, we turned
a powerful enemy into an ally.
That acar breeze is nice, you know?
Yeah, you got that right.
I had a funny feeling we'd be
the ones riding on the roof.
We're a skosh over capacity now,
so we had to strap a twin or
two to the roof of the wagon.
Well, Boxxo, you've
really outdone yourself.
I bet driving at a max speed through an
empty field would be quite exhilarating.
Hello there.
Boxxo, I'm sorry for what I did.
It's bad enough that I tried to use you,
but I also betrayed my friends
and the people of the dungeon.
I don't expect you to trust me again, but
I swear my backstabbing days are over.
I mean, my son is still a factor,
so maybe swear was the wrong word.
I trust you anyway.
That's what friends are for.
Good point.
I suppose if Master Boxo has faith
in you, I will too. We're good.
He has no reason to betray us so
long as Sulream is on our side.
I trust him, despite everything.
Huh.
Lamas and Co are ready
to forgive and forget.
But things are a little more
complicated for the former fools.
Evie?
Shwee? Pity?
I'm sorry for abandoning
and betraying all of you.
I don't deserve forgiveness.
I know it won't help,
but I'm sorry as well.
Same goes for me!
I'm sorry too!
I am also very sorry!
You're misreading the situation.
That isn't the reason we're
still upset with you whatsoever.
Shui, it appears you'll have
to spell it out for him.
Are you too dense to
figure out why we're upset?
It hurts that you didn't trust
us enough to confide in us!
If we'd known what you were planning,
we would have tried our
hardest to talk you out of it!
If it had been a half-decent plan, we
would have been right there with you!
Instead, you chose to keep it
all inside and push us away!
I have also encouraged Shui's wrath for
hiding things, like my love of footwear.
We are literally called
the Menagerie of Fools.
There's no reason to be coy about
our problems or shortcomings.
We deserve to know everything.
Although, perhaps we don't need every
detail about your amorous adventures.
I, for one, do need every detail
about those amorous adventures.
What do you know?
Marksa must have dispensed
a sense of humor for Heavy.
So, anyway, in short, Heavy,
Swee, and Petty, thank you.
We're grateful that you still
care enough to get mad at us.
It really means a lot.
What about pity?
When I asked for advice,
everyone just got loud and angry.
Darling, we're not done.
Tell me about those amorous adventures.
So ended the dramatic plot twist
with a whole menagerie of fools.
No one's saying there are
no sore feelings left,
but at least the Cap and his fools
are back on the right side of history.
Several days later, Captain Kerioyl and
his fam were already on their feet again.
They even started training with us.
As for the Ice Lady, she's
sticking to Kai like superglue.
Not exactly being chatty, but at
least she's not trying to kill us.
There's no need to be on
your guard, Magic Box.
I have no intention of
launching an attack.
I no longer serve the Demon Lord.
As such, I cannot afford
to make more enemies.
No matter what happens, I pick you swear
I'll always be on your side, big sis.
You're so precious to me.
You're all that I need.
That's one way to turn a villain.
It's pretty clear she'd never betray him.
Our journey's going smoothly, I think.
There are no monsters or roadblocks.
Just us and the long, straight road.
This cruise could have used some
blue skies and green fields,
But it's total darkness,
other than the headlights and
the warm glow of magic items.
There's an end, isn't there?
I mean, there's gotta be, right?
Look, up ahead!
Am I dreaming or is that a wall?
I was starting to think
we'd never make it.
Shame here.
Looks like the middle
path was the right idea.
There's no way to know if this really
means we've reached the Inner Depths.
Eddie's devastated.
I wanted to travel a whole
lot longer with Boxxo.
If we encounter any foes,
worry not. I'll take them.
What kind of weirdness awaits?
Alright, I'm gonna try
to manhandle it open.
I'm not seeing any traps,
but please be cautious. Hmm.
I'm trying my best to make it open,
but the thing isn't even budging.
If Llamas' strength isn't enough,
perhaps there's some special step
we must take to unlock it first.
That shape, it makes me think
there's something that goes in there.
We gave the doors the once over.
But the only things that stood out.
Were those wacky cavities.
There's just gotta be something.
That perfectly matches
that size and shape.
Insert coins.
The stratum lord coins.
I've got a hot hunch brewing.
And it's screaming at me.
This is what those stratum coins are for.
It's too big and hot.
I'm gonna be a little more.
I'm gonna be so busy.
I'm gonna be a new story.
I'll be a new story.
I can't wait. I can't wait.
I can't wait.
Oh?
Thank you so
much for
watching.
I look forward to serving you again.